[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is a View?",
    "correctAnswer": "The basic building block of the UI",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "Refers to the current page you are seeing in the app",
      "The combination of an Activity and its Fragment(s)",
      "Another term for an Activity"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is a ViewGroup?",
    "correctAnswer": "A container that can hold other views",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "Layouts files that are similar in nature",
      "Refers to the current page you are seeing in the app",
      "The combination of an Activity and its Fragment(s)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which of these is not a ViewGroup?",
    "correctAnswer": "Button",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "ConstraintLayout",
      "FrameLayout",
      "RecyclerView"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What is the difference between margin and padding.",
    "correctAnswer": "Padding is the space inside the container, while margin is the space outside of the container",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "Margin is the space inside the container, while padding is the space outside of the container",
      "They function similarly, but padding is the legacy version of margin",
      "Margin must be scaled with dp and padding must be scaled with px"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What is dp?",
    "correctAnswer": "Density-Independent Pixels, based on the physical density of the screen",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "Dimension Pixels, based on the physical dimension of the screen",
      "Design Principles, guidelines to follow for building concise UI",
      "'dp' is not used in Android"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What is sp?",
    "correctAnswer": "Scalable-Independent Pixels, scaled to the font size preference of the user",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "Synchronized Process, a variable used to synchronize certain functions in the background",
      "Scope Principles, guidelines to follow for building concise applications",
      "'sp' is not used in Android"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "When would you use 'dp' and 'sp'",
    "correctAnswer": "'sp' is used for scaling text size, 'dp' is used to scale everything else",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "'dp' is used for scaling text size, 'sp' is used to scale everything else",
      "The can be used interchangeably with not much noticeable difference",
      "Neither are used much in modern Android development"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What is a LinearLayout?",
    "correctAnswer": "A layout that arranges its elements based on the set horizontal or vertical orientation",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "A layout used to contain a single item and block off the space for it to be displayed",
      "A layout that arranges elements relative to parent or other elements",
      "A layout used to build complex layouts with a flat hierarchy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is a FrameLayout?",
    "correctAnswer": "A layout used to contain a single item and block off the space for it to be displayed",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "A layout that arranges its elements based on the set horizontal or vertical orientation",
      "A layout that arranges elements relative to parent or other elements",
      "A layout used to build complex layouts with a flat hierarchy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What does not describe a ConstraintLayout?",
    "correctAnswer": "A layout that can ignore the required attributes of a view",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "A layout that arranges elements relative to parent or other elements",
      "A layout used to build complex layouts with a flat hierarchy",
      "A layout that renders its Views faster than other layouts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "What are the required attributes of a View?",
    "correctAnswer": "android:layout_width and android:layout_height",
    "incorrectAnswers":
    [
      "The tag of the View and android:id",
      "xmlns:android=\"http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android\"",
      "val variableName: View = findViewById()"
    ]
  }
]